<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Musings of a Catalan Londoner in Prague</title><link>https://blog.melindro.com/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Musings of a Catalan Londoner in Prague</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.melindro.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About names</title><link>https://blog.melindro.com/post/about-names/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.melindro.com/post/about-names/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have a name. No surprises there. My partner also has a name. No surprises there either. What is surprising is the amount of trouble our names have given us on our adventures in the three countries we have lived our lives: Spain, England and the Czech Republic. I had an incident recently that made me think of this again and I though it would be interesting to write about it a little bit.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Note&lt;/strong>: I have not used real names here but made up ones that would be typical of Catalan and Czech people.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Relocating in the middle of a worldwide pandemic</title><link>https://blog.melindro.com/post/relocate-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.melindro.com/post/relocate-pandemic/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Bernat and I am a software developer born in Barcelona who moved to London in 2012 when my life was in desperate need of a radical change.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For a variety of reasons, me and my family decided that April 2020 was the right time to relocate again, this time to the Czech Republic. We had it all planned: we would go to Prague, do some flat viewings, give notice to our landlord to leave the current flat, then go back to London to wrap things up there, and finally leave the UK at the end of April to start a new life in Prague.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And then The Apocalypse started&amp;hellip;&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>